{
    "id": "1fb2bbfb21c444beb6c55155973eb8ab",
    "title": "Prepositions And Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We haven’t seen him ……………………. last month.",
            "description": "Since shows the starting point of time. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc0e5c983ca64cbcbc9c4d2c3a1f7f19"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. it is raining, we cannot go out now.",
            "description": "As and since can show the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "023240fbc6544fa0b580229185112a21"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… it was a holiday, I did some reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a602379eee4f478ca0acb6fb29f1f5a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did not study well ……………………… he was lazy.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "if",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b2541226ba24817a7e396763d0f00ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "He walked slowly ……………………… he was ill.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5017347b4faf4578ad4300f15f69e4cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The oranges ………………………… you gave me yesterday were very sweet.",
            "description": "Either that or which can refer to objects in identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53d1ee151a3e44568af683459ed355dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam, …………………….. we met on the train, is an architect.",
            "description": "Whom is the correct answer. Who is possible here in an informal style. That cannot be used in non-identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "that",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1de084ab8ba4cc69df3c8867c5dd20a"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I was in Spain, I visited many museums there.",
            "description": "While can mean at the same time that.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45ecdeb8acdf4ee9bc3b92c6b0a0852d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… the rain has stopped, we can resume the match.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Now that",
                "Now",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30d47ea8ed094fdca99524da8b4d9113"
        },
        {
            "question": "He does not know any language …………………….. Hindi.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "except",
                "in addition",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d064bc378ffb4980aac7df581362ddc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you start now, you will miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4d04cad3a6b4b84b9dbb775d703ea66"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… he is immensely rich, he leads a simple life.",
            "description": "Even if refers to past even though refers to future. ",
            "answers": [
                "Even though",
                "Even if",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49eed522fbdd478ab0d76d0f2702e906"
        }
    ]
}